http://www.teenhealthfx.com/privacy.html

Bullying & Violence Websites
Emergency Help!
Helping Friends And Loved Ones With Their Emotional Issues
Helping Friends/Loved Ones Who Are Suicidal Or In Abusive Situations
For Teens, By Teens
General:
Cancer
COVID-19 (Coronavirus)
Feces, Poop & Butt Issues
Hairy Situations:
Name That Symptom
Other Skin Conditions: Moles, Birthmarks, Dryness, Etc.
+-
Concerned About A Friend / Concerned About A Friend's Influence On Me
Dealing With Divorce, Step-Parents and Step-Siblings
Difficulties In Making Friends & Not Enough Time With Friends
Sibling Issues
Significant Others:
Penis & Testicle Concerns
Pregnancy: Could I Be Pregnant?
Pregnancy: General Pregnancy And Pregnancy Prevention Questions/Concerns
Being A Vegetarian
Body Weight - What's Normal?
Problematic Eating Habits
Questions On Vitamins, Nutrients, Additives And Specific Foods
Underweight/Overweight: Affecting Your Mind And body
What You Should Know About Diet Aides And Certain Diet Tactics
+-
Could I Be Pregnant?
How Soon Can You Test For STDs?
Benefits of Eating Breakfast Before School
Teen Collects 10k Masks for Those In Need!
COVID-19: How Teens Can Protect Their Mental Health
Trivia!
Who We Are
Have a Question?
Resources
Emergency Help!
Have a Question?
Home
Resources
Emergency Help!
Privacy
TeenHealthFX.com Web site is maintained by Atlantic Health System, 475 South Street, Morristown, New Jersey. Atlantic can be reached by our feedback portal here.
OUR COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY:
We are dedicated to maintaining the privacy of our users.
HOW TeenHealthFX.com USES INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU: TeenHealthFX.com or any other Atlantic Health System site does not collect personally identifiable information (for example, your name, home address, email address, etc.) about individuals except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals.
TeenHealthFX does not provide, sell or lease your personally identifiable information to any parties. TeenHealthFX collects anonymous data for statistical purposes.
REGISTRATION: Users do not have to register to use TeenHealthFX.
PARENTS: Atlantic Health System encourages you to get involved with your children's online usage and to be aware of the activities in which they are participating. You should also discourage your children from giving any personally identifiable information on the Internet. If you have any concerns about your child's or your use of www.teenhealthfx.com or any other Atlantic Health System Internet site, please contact us at info@atlantichealth.org.
When you follow a link from TeenHealthFX.com Internet site to any third-party site, you are no longer protected by TeenHealthFX.com Privacy Policy.
TeenHealthFX may make changes to this Privacy Policy. Changes will be posted on this site
70% of youth in juvenile justice systems have at least one mental health condition 6
33% of adolescents in America are victim to sexual, physical, verbal, or emotional dating abuse. 18
Nearly two in five 12th graders report using some kind of vaping device in the past year. 7
1 in 4 teens contract a sexually transmitted disease every year. 11
In 2017, persons aged 15–24 years represented 62.6% of all chlamydia cases. 10
More than 130 Americans die everyday from an opioid overdose. 9
In the next 24 hours, 1,439 teens will attempt suicide. 14
In the next 24 hours, 2,795 teenage girls will become pregnant 12
Only 50.6% of U.S. youth aged 6-17 with a mental health disorder received treatment in the last year. 8
90% of daily tobacco users begin by age 18 13
Many teens reported feeling overwhelmed (31%) and depressed or sad (30%) as a result of stress. 16
37.3 percent of 12th graders reported vaping in the past 12 months 15
Two-thirds of those who developed alcohol or substance use disorders have had a mental health disorder. 17
In 2016, 56 percent of deaths among passenger vehicle occupants ages 16-19 were drivers 22
21% of all new HIV diagnoses in the U.S. are among people aged 13-24 years old, most of those being 20-24. 19
59% of all students in grades 9 to 12 indicated that they had not yet had sex. 21
1 in 3 young people will be in an abusive or unhealthy relationship 23
50% of young people who experience rape or physical or sexual abuse will attempt to commit suicide 24
There was a 78% increase in e-cigarette use between 2017 and 2018. 2
1 in 6 U.S. youth aged 6-17 experience a mental health disorder each year. 1
Suicide is the second leading cause of death for youth ages 12-18.  3
Young people aged 15–24 years acquire half of all new STDs 4
In 2017, 5455 teenagers died from an overdose 5
44.88% of teens feel stressed “all the time.” 25
59% of U.S. teens have personally experienced at least one type of abusive online behaviors. 26
In 2017 2,734 teenagers (ages 13-19) died in the United States from crash injuries. 27
Roughly 40% of teenagers will try drugs at least once, which means 60% will not. 28
The average 12th grader spends approximately 2 hours per day texting. 29
feedback
legal
privacy
Copyright 2020 Atlantic Health System
